{
    "subject": "resource/Victoria_Marchenkova",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Young_Clever",
    "human_readable": "Victoria Marchenkova's movement is Young Clever.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9646661877632141,
            "question": "Are there any notable figures associated with the 'Young Clever' movement besides Victoria Marchenkova?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8662312626838684,
            "question": "Is Victoria Marchenkova involved in a specific movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8657111525535583,
            "question": "What is Victoria Marchenkova's movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7630398869514465,
            "question": "What defines the 'Young Clever' movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7023294568061829,
            "question": "Describe the movement that Victoria Marchenkova is part of."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6987979412078857,
            "question": "What is the name of the movement associated with Victoria Marchenkova?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6701481938362122,
            "question": "To which movement does Victoria Marchenkova belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5877094268798828,
            "question": "What are some characteristics or values typically associated with the 'Young Clever' movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5029892325401306,
            "question": "How might the 'Young Clever' movement influence or be influenced by current trends?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38637202978134155,
            "question": "What can you tell about Victoria Marchenkova's artistic or social affiliations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Victoria Marchenkova's movement is Young Clever.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8734_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might the 'Young Clever' movement influence or be influenced by current trends?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8734_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics or values typically associated with the 'Young Clever' movement?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8734_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which movement does Victoria Marchenkova belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8734_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8734_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8734_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8734_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8734_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8734_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8734_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8734_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8734_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8734_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8734_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Victoria is a prominent representative of \u2018Young&Clever\u2019 Wave,\" which supports the triple that Victoria Marchenkova's movement is referred to as Young Clever."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Victoria Marchenkova's movement is not specifically identified as \"Young Clever\" within the provided context. It is mentioned that she is a prominent representative of the 'Young&Clever' Wave, but there isn't any evidence to suggest that this specific term 'Young Clever' refers to an official art movement associated with Victoria Marchenkova.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states she is a \"prominent representative of \u2018Young&Clever\u2019 Wave.\"",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It contradicts the information provided in section 5 of the context.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context states that Victoria Marchenkova made a shift from contextual to avant-garde positions, not that her movement is Young Clever.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}